Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
- Series II. Assignments
  - Postharvest losses reduction short course group photo., Sept. 9, 1988; 1414; 4 (Box 25)
  - ALScapades and Outstanding Alumni Awards Banquet., Sept, 16, 17,18, 1988; 1415; 269 (Box 25)
  - HE Hotline Students: Sheet#1: Frames 1-8 Stefania Bloom, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#1: Frames 9-16: Lisa Hamburg, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 3-10: Robert Milstein, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 11-18: Karen Lauster, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 20-21: Lee Godlewski, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 2 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#3: Frames 22-29: Lee Godlewski, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#3: Frames 30-35: Lori Rolleri, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 4 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#3: Frames 36-38: Matt Golden, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 2 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#4: Frames 5-8: Matt Golden, Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 3 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#4: Frames 13-17: Rick Delsesto., Sept. 7, 1988; 1416; 4 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#5: Michelle Dowling., Sept. 19, 1988; 1416; 6 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#6: Lori Rolleri, Sept. 26, 1989; 1416; 9 (Box 25)
  - Sheet #7: Frames 19-23: Michelle Marshall, Jan. 25, 1989; 1416; 3 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#7: Frames 24-33: Cewin Chao, Jan. 25, 1989; 1416; 7 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 34-4: Karen Little, Jan. 25, 1989; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 18-24: Michael Sanders, Jan. 25, 1989; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#9: Frames 8-18: Karen Khu, Jan. 25, 1989; 1416; 7 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#9: Frames 20-25 Steve Merz., Jan. 25, 1989; 1416; 4 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#10: Winifed Lloyds, Jan. 25, 1989; 1416; 5 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#11: Ed Requet., Feb. 9, 1989; 1416; 6 (Box 25)
  - Teaching convocation - group shots, candids, presentations., Sept. 14, 1989; 1417; 63 (Box 25)
  - Portrait of Fjames C. Pratt., Sept. 16, 1989; 1418; 5 (Box 25)
  - BTI Annual Report. Sheets#1,2,3: Exterior plots, research photos. BTI research fields off Dryden Rd- Environmental Biology research on Red Spruce and Sugar Maple trees., Sept, 15, 1988; 1419; 74 (Box 25)
  - Sheets 4-10: BTI research photos - see list in file., Feb. 7,8,9, 1989; 1419; 209 (Box 25)
  - Personal Enterprise Porum with Marjorie Blanchard as Kay Note Speaker. Sheets 1,2,3., Sept. 19, 1988; 1420; 41 color; 25 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#4: Board of Directors Meeting., Sept. 10, 1988; 1420; 17 color, 10 (Box 25)
  - Century Farms 1988: Sheet#1: Jefferson Co. farm - Henry Adams, Jr. Dairy Farm., Aug. 24, 1988; 1421; 19 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#2: Orange County: Mark Roe farm (apples), Sept. 8, 1988; 1421; 24 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#3: Livingston County: Jon White farm, Sept. 13, 1988; 1421; 15 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#4: Seneca County: David Eastman Farms., Sept. 20, 1988; 1421; 27 (Box 25)
  - Portrait of Mike Newman - Manager of Facilities Eng. Computer Section, Oct. 7, 1988; 1422; 12 (Box 25)
  - Exhibits: Sheet#1: Urban Horticulture, School Youth, Kids Don't Come With Directions, Food For Health, Efnep is Nutrition Education, Helping Consumers Make Healthy Food Choices, Working With Teen Parents, Efnep Makes a Difference, Managing Money Matters, Compost Facts., Sept. 1988; 1423; 21 CN (Box 25)
  - Sheet#2: Dept. of Communications, Nutrition for Life, 4 4-H Plant Science Exhibits, Gov. Cuomo, Pat Moore at computer, screen and Tompkins County poster., Jan. 1999; 1423; 26 cn (Box 25)
  - Sheet#3: HE forum folding exhibit., Apr. 1989; 1423; 2 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#4: 4-H Pant Sciences Sportsfishing, NY Farm Net, Blank Panals, Horticulture exhibits., Apr. 14, 1989; 1423; 9 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#5: Human Ecology Beginnings Exhibit., May 1989; 1423; 5 (Box 25)
  - Dean Call with Walter Coward with 5 Chinese visitors in Dean Call's office, Oct. 20, 1988; 1424; 13 (Box 25)
  - Janet Brown portrait - taken for an employee award, Oct. 26, 1988; 1425; 8 (Box 26)
  - CALS Award Presentation given to Pres. Rhodes, Dean Call, Joe Hoskiss, Bob Gravani by State Police Capt. Art Pierce., Oct. 26, 1988; 1426; 8; 6cn (Box 26)
  - Media Services staff/ taken for Visa Prints. Sheet#1: Frames 15-18: Gordon Webb - Supervisor Radio CTR., Oct. 27, 1988; 1427; 3 (Box 26)
  - Frames 10-13: Robert Eaton - Broadcast Ent. ETV, .; 1427; 3 (Box 26)
  - Frames 5-8 Dan Booth - manager Broadcast production, .; 1427; 3 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#2: David Watkins- Director of Media Services, Nov. 1988; 1427; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#3: Close-up of handkerchief of DW jacket, Oct. 25, 1988; 1427; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#4: Dan Booth sitting at switcher in ETV studio., Apr. 26, 1989; 1427; 14 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#5: Satellite truck sitting up at plantation/ some with dish up, Apr. 26, 1989; 1427; 20 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#6: New TV camera/Eric Gastieger & Mike Veeley, Apr. 28, 1989; 1427; 19 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#7: Dennis Kulis and Lorraine Heasley in Design Studio., May 7, 1989; 1427; 20 (Box 26)
  - Cornell Federal Credit Union staff photos taken for use in newsletter. Sheet#1: Frames 7-13c. Deward Maynard - member of Board of Directors for CFCU. Frames 15-18: Harold Roberts - member of Board of Directors for CFCU., Nov. 17, 1988; 1428; 8 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#2: Harold Roberts: Frames 2-5. Frames 6-17- Gil Senger - Candidate for Board of Directors for CFCU. Frames 19-20: Barbara Hinman- staff member CFCU, Nov. 17, 1988; 1428; 12 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#3: Barbara Hinman, Nov. 17, 1988; 1428; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#4: Robert Witty - Pres. Cornell Fed. Credit Union, Nov. 17, 1988; 1428; 6 (Box 26)
  - Sheets #5&6: Portrait of David Chatterton: Member of CFCU., Dec. 2, 1988; 1428; 15 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#7: Frames 2-7: Mary Oberhaus: Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#7:Frames 8-13: Pat Stage: Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#7:Frames 15-20: Lori Fisher; Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 21-24: Lori Fisher - Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 3 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 25-30: Cindy Switzer - Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 32-38: Nancy Snyder: Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 5 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#9: Frames 1-5: Nancy Snyder: Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 3 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#9: Frames 6-18: Barbara inman - Credit Union Manager., Feb. 15, 1989; 1428; 9 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#10: Portrait of Ronald B. Furry: Prof. Of Ag. & Bio. Engineering., Feb. 28, 1989; 1428; 11 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#11: Jill Ciccone - Personnel Director Credit Union. Frames 1-9., Apr. 27, 1989; 1428; 6 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#11: Frames 10-18: Penny Chick- Marketing Director., Apr. 27, 1989; 1428; 6 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#12: Portrait of John Tucker: manager Loan Dept., June 5, 1989; 1428; 7 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Donald Specker/ Entomology Dept. & Tioga County, Oct. 25, 1988; 1429; 11 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Dale Riggs - Regional Extension Specialist in Albany., Oct. 27, 1988; 1430; 8 (Box 26)
  - New Agents: Pro Dairy. Sheet:1: Frames 2-7: Nate Leonard - Lewis County. Frames 8-12: Clint Young - Cornell University. Frames 17-20: Guy Hutt - Cornell University. Sheet#2: Frames 21-26: Guy Hutt, Cornell University. Frames 27-32: Beth Claypole - Cornell University. Frames 34-39: Lee Tlega - Albany Regional Office., Dec. 14, 1988; 1431; 12 (Box 26)
  - China Group Photo: Sheet2: Candids with China group., Dec. 16, 1989; 1432; 5 (Box 26)
  - Cooperative Extension representatives, Jan 10, 1989; 1433; 5 (Box 26)
  - Media Services trip to China with Cornell Glee Club, Jan. 1989; 1434; 513 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Betsy Hart - Ag. Economics Office Assistant for Home Study., Feb. 1, 1989; 1435; 4 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of David L. Brown, Professor of Rural Sociology, Asso. Prof. Research Office, Asso. Prof. Agr. Exp. Station, Ithaca, NY., Feb. 7, 1989; 1436; 6 (Box 26)
  - Presentation to Dean Call from Paul Tilly - Pres. Of Alumni Association and Robert Nagler, Chairman of Alumni Assoc., Feb. 16, 1989; 1437; 17 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Peter Trowbridge - Prof. Of Floriculture., Feb. 16, 1989; 1438; 5 (Box 26)
  - Portraits of Ray Oglesby - Prof. Natural Resources on frames 33a-4; Dan Aneshansley - Assoc. prof. Of Ag. And Bio. Engineering frames 4a-9., Feb. 28, 1989; 1439; 13 (Box 26)
  - American Greeting reps presentation of plaque to student. American Greeting reps: Howard Green and Bil Parsons. Student: Anne Marie Farrell and Gene German - Ag. Eco., Mar. 13, 1989; 1440; 6 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Prof. Frank Becker - DEA., Mar. 13, 1989; 1441; 7 (Box 26)
  - TXA Pesticides Exhibit - [photos. Frames 2-8: Washing machine with coveralls, Frames 9-15: Mike Powers reading label in pesticides bottle, Frames 16-25: David Lynch - Benjamin with HE Grad student reading manual., Mar. 3,8, 1989; 1442; 24 (Box 26)
  - New Dairy Center opening in Stocking Hall/opening ceremony, speakers, audience, and tour of facility - candids., Mar. 14, 1989; 1443; 49 (Box 26)
  - AD White Professors at large - Sheets 1&2: Prof. At large Ali Mazrue speaking in Goldwin Smith Hall, also office portrait and still., Mar. 2&9, 1989; 1444; 41 (Box 26)
  - Wellness Day photos for the Society for Nutrition Education / undergrads., Mar. 13, 1989; 1445; 65 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Richard Roush- Asst. Prof. Entomology, Mar. 22, 1989; 1446; 18 (Box 26)
  - In-Depth workshop- photos of speaker, panel, and candids of participants., Mar. 21, 1989; 1447; 20 (Box 26)
  - Mac screen / full image plus people working at terminals in Mann Library., Mar. 24, 1989; 1448; 23 (Box 26)
  - Anne Matthews and Clarence Reed outside Comstock Hall for use in the "Staffing for the Future" brochure., Apr. 4, 1989; 1449; 9 (Box 26)
  - Mary McFadden, a NYS apparel designer, in classroom with students; exhibit and opening of M. McFadden's work in MVR Gallery with her interacting with people., Apr. 3&4, 1989; 1450; 100 (Box 26)
  - Frank Shipe symposium at Sheraton Ballroom., Apr. 3&4, 1989; 1451; 155 (Box 26)
  - Chair-caning shot in the photo studio., Apr. 12, 1989; 1452; 12 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#1: Portrait of Judy Bandas/Extension Asso. /Field Instructor., Apr. 17, 1989; 1453; 8 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#2: Portrait of Tom Hanna/Executive Staff Assistant, Apr. 17, 1989; 1453; 7 (Box 26)
  - Minority Brochure photos - students in classroom with Prof. Ileen Devault, also students in Student Organizational meeting. Shs 1 & 2., Apr. 13, 1989; 1454; 68 (Box 26)
  - Sheets 3,4,5: Hosting Program: students considering enrollment at CU., Apr. 21, 1989; 1454; 58 (Box 26)
  - New Food Science Lab Photos: Sheet#1: Frames 1-11: Lab technician making cheese curls. Frames 13-20 and Sheet#2 ice cream in the making with lab tech and students. Sheet#3: Ice cream. Cheese curls., Apr. 25, 1989; 1455; . (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Prof. Edgar Raffensperger/Entomology, Apr. 4, 1989; 1456; 8 (Box 26)
  - Portraits of HE students: Sheet#1: Maddy Echshein, May 4, 1989; 1457; 4 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#2: Susan Scheiedel, May 9, 1989; 1457; 6 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#3: HE senior Richard Safeer, May 24, 1989; 1457; 5 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#4: HE senior Richard Safeer in lab in HE., May 24, 1989; 1457; 7 (Box 26)
  - Five Navy ROTC men in full uniform/full length photos. Sheet#1: Frames 2-10: Robert Rovira. Frames 12-18: Jose Rolfon. Frame 20: Sean Forbes., May 11, 1989; 1458; 12 (Box 26)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 21-24: Sean Forbes. Frames 25-30: Mark Stingle. Frames 32-38: Bryan Kimura, May 11, 1989; 1458; 12 (Box 26)
  - Dr. Bruce Ames - Prof. Of Bio Chemistry at Berkeley University. Informal setting with students., May 16, 1989; 1459; 37 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Dr. Andre Jagendorf - Prof. Plant Physiology and Chairman also Liberty Hyde Bailey Professor., May 25, 1989; 1460; 10 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Elizabeth Oltenacu - Assoc. Prof. Animal Science and Associate Director for Academic Programs in Roberts Hall., May 30, 1989; 1461; 12 (Box 26)
  - Retirement parties for Marge Devine/DNS. Party was held at Helen Newman lounge. (Sheets# 1,2,&3). Peggy Haines's band played., May 19, 1989; 1462; 105 (Box 26)
  - Sheets #4&5: Retirement party for Marcia Pimental / DNS held in the MVR Faculty Lounge., May 24,1989; 1462; 63 (Box 26)
  - Photo of Prof. Archie R. Ammons - English Dept., May 24,1989; 1463; 11 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of David Blanford / Prof. Of Ag. Economics., June 16, 1989; 1464; 6 (Box 26)
  - Compensation Conference Opening Night Dinner, May 23, 1989; 1465; 34 (Box 26)
  - ILR Alumni Reception and Dedication of Faculty Lounge Room #280 which is now the Robert E. Doherty Room., June 89, 1989; 1466; 29 (Box 26)
  - Two Food Science Grads/Sheet#1: Anne Roland / Sheet#2: Mike Halser., June 6, 1989; 1467; 17 (Box 26)
  - ILR Grads carrying ILR Banner during procession / ILR Graduation ceremony., May 28, 1989; 1468; 63 (Box 26)
  - Leaders Institute for Food Science, June 16, 1989; 1469; 108 (Box 26)
  - 1989 CALS Alumni Display in Barton Hall, June 9, 989; 1470; 33 (Box 26)
  - 1989 ALS Reunion breakfast and board meeting at Sheraton Inn. Also sign that says only 200 seats left for Alumni Auditorium., June 10, 1989; 1471; 77 (Box 26)
  - HE News Sheets#1: 1,2,3,4: HE Graduation Procession with Dean Firebaugh and students., May 28, 1989; 1472; 92 (Box 26)
  - Sheets#5,6,7: Sheet#5: Child Abuse Seminar and TXA Seminar. Sheets 6&7- Alumni Board Meeting., June 9, 1989; 1472; 85 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Linda Waugh - Prof. Of Modern Languages and Ling., July 10, 1989; 1473; 5 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Jane Powers: Research Support Specialist in HDFS., July 10, 1989; 1474; 5 (Box 26)
  - Portrait of Enrique Figuerosa - Asst. Prof. Ag. Eco., July 26, 1989; 1475; 11 (Box 26)
  - Reception for summer students in MVR faculty lounge, July 27, 1989; 1476; 42 (Box 26)
  - Color negs made from DA's color shots of various extension activities around county and campus., July 1989; 1477; 11 (Box 26)
  - Food Executive Program, reception, clambake, dinner, etc., July 16, 1989; 1478; 250 (Box 26)
  - Vet School lab scenes/ Equine Research Farm., July/Aug. 1989; 1479; 104 (Box 26)
- Series III. Slides and Miscellany
  - Negatives and photographs (Box 27)
  - Slides, slide sets, and out-takes (Box 28)
  - Slides (Box 29)
  - Slides (Box 30)
- Series IV. Bulletins
  - Bulletins 0-700. (Box Box 31)
  - Bulletins 701-750. (Box Box 32)
  - Bulletins 751-800. (Box Box 33)
  - Bulletins 801-870. (Box Box 34)
  - Bulletins 871-970. (Box Box 35)
  - Bulletins 971-1080. (Box Box 36)
  - Bulletins 1081-1200. (Box Box 37)
  - Farm and Home Week Exhibits (Box Box 38)